jobego.com 2013-05-15

# Jobego

Jobego.com Privacy Policy

What Personal Information We Collect

When you sign up for the Jobego (The Company) you will be required to share information that identifies you personally. "Personal Information" refers to any information that lets us know the specifics of who you are and which can be used to identify, contact or locate you. Users may be also required to provide subsequent demographic such as, but is not limited to: birth date, gender, marital status, education completed, household income, and number of children in household.

Use of Information

Generally, we collect Personal Information when you provide it to us by signing up on Jobego.com (The Website), filling out surveys or using any other services. We usually collect Personal Information so that it can provide you with the Company's goods or services. If you don't provide some of the Personal Information we ask for (e.g. your name, your mailing address and/or email address), it may be unable to provide you with our goods or services.

Protection of Information

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

Sharing of Information

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

Third Party Links and Advertisements

We may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. While the Company makes every effort to ensure that its advertisers post clear and complete privacy policies and observe appropriate data practices, each of these sites has a privacy policy that may differ from that of the Company. The privacy practices of other websites and companies are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please be aware that the Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

Cookies

The Company may set and access cookies on your computer. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. We use cookies to help us provide personalized features and preferences.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update this Policy from time to time.
